[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Did you ever feel when you were working so closely with this man that you would ever have to say the words you just said about him, that he is effectively an enemy combatant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Or do you believe that there should be a way of stopping him being able to use this as a platform to attack America, to attack American servicemen, and to potentially rally the enemy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "TO", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, I do to a degree.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "From a legal standpoint is there anything that can be done to stop him turning this into a show trial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, I think the staff sergeant had it right that the judge was just doing her duty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Who would you bet on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Is expecting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "How well did you know Tamerlan Tsarnaev and what changes did you see him go through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I knew Tamerlan very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "So you could see signs then that he was getting more aggressive perhaps?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "He had always been kind of, like John said, walked the line between clock cocky and arrogant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "or had part of you always feared that he may be capable of not necessarily an atrocity like that but something bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "On the contrary, I never saw it coming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Did you see any of that, either of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Michael, there's also this connection to the triple homicide which happened on September 11, 2011, where once of the victims, Brendan Mess, also had a connection to the gym, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "WRB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "That is correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September 11, 2011"], "PERSON": ["Michael", "Brendan Mess"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "And the belief now is that Tamerlan may well have been involved in his murder and the murder of two others at the same time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "That's what the authorities are saying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Did you meet her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I met her maybe two or three times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Was he very much, as many have suggested, in his older brother's thrall?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "And what do you think has happened here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "A young woman in her 30s went out to run an errand that any mother would at just before 3:00 in the morning and was never seen again alive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "One, I would disagree with them because whenever there is a mother who leaves three children in such a gruesome and brutal way the local media will jump on it right away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bouchard"]}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "``", "NN", "DT", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 378, "question": "How is the investigation going into Rhonda's death?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Piers, I'm telling you, when I spoke with Sheriff Bouchard today, he said that they are, quote, \"dogging this case.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rhonda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "But there's a point that if America saw the reality it could change things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I would never presume to tell a parent how they should feel or how they should emotionally react.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Does it help his party that he hasn't parachuted a Republican in here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ":", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Tell me, Margaret, I mean, is he already emerging as the compelling candidate to fight the next general election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "He is certainly emerging -- well, in a general election absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016", "2012"]}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "What -- what could stop him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "-- in 2016 than it did in 2012.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Smith"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Well, what could stop him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Well, I mean -- there's this me amongst Republicans that all of his behavior will stop him now, by not appointing a Republican like Chris Smith, the New Jersey congressman, that won't stop him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "But if they want to win -- Marc, if they want to win the election, isn't this what someone like him has to be doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "WP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ":", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "How did America get so mediocre?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "You know, I think parents -- both parents started working.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "I mean, it's just an idiot thing to say, wasn't it, Margaret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Well, it's the stupid face on an important debate which is work-life balance.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "If Americans saw the reality of a mass shooting outrage, could it change public opinion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNPS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I think public opinion has been changed already just by knowing that those 6-year-olds, those babies were killed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "What he's saying is what will change the debate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBZ", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Here's the -- here's the difference, though, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Where do you draw the line there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Well, I think first of all common decency is you have to defer to the parents.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.S. Supreme Court"], "PERSON": ["Dohmann"]}, "docId": "130604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", ":", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Do these two stories today, two completely different stories, but joined if you like by the sense of, isn't it great that in modern America now, quite rapidly actually, we can celebrate both those things and it seems relatively normal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "NN", ",", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Days before the U.S. Supreme Court will rule on two important gay rights cases, the Dohmann case and the Prop 8 case about whether, you know, some of these laws will be overturned, you have, by the way, 120 -- 222 Republican legislators across the country have voted for freedom to marry, transgender, bisexual rights.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]